请个人来盘问凯里
Hire someone to cross-examine Cary,
看看他能不能坚持住
see if he holds up.
什么    你...艾丽西娅
What, are you...? Alicia.
你不是说不接案子了吗
I thought you weren't taking any more cases.
我是不接了
I'm not.
我只是要支持这姑娘一小时
I just need to hand-hold this girl for an hour,
我马上就进去了
and I'll be right in.
艾丽西娅  你也太不负责任了  什么案子
Alicia, this is so irresponsible. What is the case?
强奸案
Rape.
真棒  强奸案真是"从不会引发争议"呢
Oh, great, because rape is never controversial.
艾丽西娅·福瑞克的律所合伙人目前正被
Would it change your mind to know that Alicia Florrick's
州检起诉  知道了这件事你会改变主意吗
law partner is being prosecuted by the State's Attorney?
他被起诉的罪名是什么
What is he being prosecuted for?
罪名是面对分销价值130万美元海洛因的毒贩
For telling drug dealers how to avoid arrest for the sale
教其如何躲避追捕
and distribution of $1.3 million in heroin.